COLLIN HODGSON

Contact

Address

3558 N 875 E Ogden, UT, 84414

Phone

801-792-5502

E-mail

collinhodgs@gmail.com

Portfolio

https://collinhodgson.github.io/React-Portfolio/

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/collinhodgson/

GitHub

https://github.com/Collin-Hodgson

Skills

API/JSON, Bootstrap,
Command Line, CSS,
Express.js, GIT, GitHub,
Heroku, HTML, HTML5,
JavaScript, JQuery,
MongoDB, MySQL, Node.js,
React, SEO

Recently graduated a Full Stack Web Developer program at the University of Utah and received certificate of completion. Committed to high standards of user experience, usability, and speed. Lends detailed knowledge of SEO to increase visibility. Detail focused and ambitious problem solver with a passion for online businesses, and would like to join a team of like-minded developers.

Education

2020-05 - Coding Bootcamp Full Stack Developer Certificate

University of Utah - Salt Lake City, UT

2014-08 -2018-12

Associate of Science

Weber State University - Ogden, UT

Work History

2020-10 -2020-11

Web Developer

Summerlin Labs, Ogden, UT

- Tasked with creating a website for a health and testing clinic
- Collaborated with colleagues to create appointment scheduling and login services for patients
- Provided front-end website development using HTML, CSS, and MDBootstrap

2019-02 -2020-03

Lighting Technician

Superior Energy & Control, Layton, UT

- Retrofitted or replaced 27,000 lights with 14 other colleagues over one year
- Tasked with going back through finished buildings to ensure lighting levels matched government standards

2015-01 -2019-01

Car Wash Attendant

Quick & Clean Car Wash, Ogden, UT

- Responsible for reviewing and reconciling weekly cash transactions, accountable for bank deposits
- Washed an average of 400 cars per shift